<?xml version ="1.0"?> 
<globals>
	<members type="array">#Ian#David</members>
	<projectname type="text">The ACM Redux</projectname>
	<about type="text"><![CDATA[
				<p><strong>What is ACM Redux?</strong> ACM Redux is the rejuvenation of the ACM website after it went down. 
				The website employs new, hand coded, systems from the layout to the database. 
				The systems employed are created to make a highly expandable, user friendly system.</p>
		       <h3>PHP DataBase Daemon - PHPDBD</h3>
		<p>The database employed is named PHPDBD. It is a PHP driven XML data storage system. That is to day, the data is stored in XML files. 
		The data is read and written by the PHPDB system. The reasoning for this system is to creat a highly portable database.  Transportation 
		of the database is as simple as compying files over. This allows moving from server to server much easier. Future iterations of the database 
		will be plug-in friendly.
		</p>
		<h3>ReduxFrameworks</h3>
		<p>The ReduxFrameworks is the front end of the website. It is a sleek, progressive layout. The look is clean, simple and user friendly. 
		The layout is of an object oriented design. This allows for easy replacement and expansion when it is needed. The layout allows for 
		ease of future use. The layout was designed with the future of ACM in mind. </p>
		
	]]></about>
	
	<abstract type="text"><![CDATA[
	<p>The ACM Redux project, started by David Nuon and Ian Goegebuer, is the reinventing of the ACM website. The goal of this project was to create a content driven modern website with new backbone architecture. <br>
	The front end and skinning design is the work of David Nuon. David created a website not unlike a program. His system involves many objects working efficiently together. The system is strong, efficient and expandable.<br>
	The backend of the website is a new PHP driven XML database system. The database is made to be easily moved, replaced and backed up. The database files are easily accessible through the file-system, allowing the user to move data efficiently.
	</p>	
	]]></abstract>
	<header type="url">/assets/img/project_sample.png</header>
	<catch type="text">Giving computing at the Beach a fresh coat of paint.</catch>
	<status type="int">0</status>
</globals>