<?xml version ="1.0"?> 
<globals>
    <name type="text">Lynn Cherngchaosil</name>
    <quote type="text">Make it run, make it right, make it fast.</quote>
    
    <discovery type="text"><![CDATA[
        <p>
            Freshman year, free pizza. I think that's how everybody finds out about ACM.
        </p>
              
    ]]></discovery>
    
    <motivation type="text"><![CDATA[
        <p>
It seems like a really cool club and it is. I have hanged out with so many cool people since the very beginning. And if not because of those people, I don't think I would be where I am today so that should explain how awesome they are.
        </p>
        
    ]]></motivation>
    <advice type="text"><![CDATA[ 
        <pre>   while(!student.isGood()){ student.keepPracticing(); }</pre>

        <p>
            I guess that's the simplest way to put it. If you're not good at something, keep doing it until you know it inside out.
        </p>

        <p>
            Oh and join our CSULB programming team, this one is super important :D.
        </p>
    ]]></advice>
    <activeyears type="text">2009-present</activeyears>
    <activity type="text"><![CDATA[ 
       <p>
            I did the Veteran Affair project. I was also a Company Liaison for a while and a Web Master, then I joined ACM-W.
       </p>
   

    ]]></activity>
    
    <desc type="text"><![CDATA[
    <p>        
    
       I really enjoy algorithms. It's one of the things if not the only thing that attracts me to this major. Last summer, I interned at Amazon and all of these algorithms had come pretty handy during the interview questions. People have called me workaholic, but I don't think I am so....I don't know. Come hang out with me and find out, I'll still be here for a little while.
    </p>
    
        
    ]]></desc>
    
    <memory type="text"><![CDATA[
        <p> 
            Probably everything, it has been such a huge part of my life that I don't think I'll ever forget any of it, especially my friends. Most of them had already graduated and I'll miss them dearly.
        </p>
         
    ]]></memory>
    
    <email type="text">pcherng00@gmail.com</email>
</globals>