<?xml version ="1.0"?> 
<globals>
    <name type="text">Joshua Liong</name>
    <quote type="text">Always at your service!</quote>
    
    <discovery type="text"><![CDATA[
        <p>
    I was introduced to the Association for Computing Machinery by Donna Pompei during CECS 274.    

	 </p>
                
    ]]></discovery>
    
    <motivation type="text"><![CDATA[
        <p>
	I have always wanted to participate in an organization to further refine my skills as a computer scientist. I knew that being active in an organization would increase my merit as a potential employee. I also felt a personal need to expand my horizons since I had no programming experience prior to my freshman year.         
</p><p>
I also had a personal goal to not be held back by any sort of fear and to be more spontaneous. When ACM began to sponsor ImagineCup projects, I tossed myself into the fire. Even with my little experience, the people of ACM were extremely supportive with helping me see that anything is possible with a little hard work and dedication. It was also fun getting to know everyone’s backgrounds and talents. 
</p>
    ]]></motivation>
    <advice type="text"><![CDATA[ 
    <p>Moderation is key. Be sure to outline explicitly what is MOST important to you and strive for excellence in everything that is important. Aristotle said &quot; You are what you repeatedly do. Excellence is, then, not an act, but a habit.&quot; One will find that opportunities will come to them when excellence is displayed. Do your best to avoid activity that is consumption-oriented and not constructive-oriented.

<p>
Don't be discouraged by setbacks, especially if it's not over. In my first semester, Professor Allison said that "It's 
never how you start the game. It's how you finish." Ensure that you have the best kind endgame in mind and never stop 
working for it. While excellence is repetitive, success is how you finish. Keep these two, and a positive attitude, in mind.
</p>

<p>
I am a firm believer of karma. Be generous with your time to others. Helping out or contributing to other people tends to reciprocate in unexpected ways. Each time you do so, you develop a connection that can help later on. Especially perceive professors as a friend and develop a good rapport with them.
</p>

	]]></advice>
    <activeyears type="text">2010-2012</activeyears>
    <activity type="text"><![CDATA[ 
<p>
<strong> Fall 2009 - Spring 2010 </strong><br/><br/>
In the year of 2009-2010, I participated in one of three ACM&rasquo; 
sponsored ImagineCup group. The ImagineCup group specialized in the Game 
Design competition; I never thought I would participate in videogame 
development; much less self-teach myself how to code. I got up every 
morning excited about what I was going to learn through TEAR , my 
videogame idea that was further fleshed out and made even more fun by 
the talented group I was working with. While TEAR did not exceed 
preliminary rounds, a discussion with my team revealed that we could 
still learn more, grow as a team and reap in rewards with continuing the 
project for next year. We pushed off more determined than ever with the 
current TEAR engine.</p>

<p><strong>Summer 2012</strong><br/><br/>
ACM exposed me to the Summer University Program taking place at 
Switzerland. In Summer 2009, I was able to get free room, board, tuition 
and spending money at Switzerland with ACM Members Lynn Cherngchaosil, 
Nathan Pickrell, Matt Sguerri and Richard Wang. This was a once in a 
lifetime opportunity of being able to travel freely while taking courses 
on challenging subjects with international students. Matt, a former 
resident of Italy, was kind enough to take us on a tour. Volkan Aginlar 
was able to plan and take many of us around many adventures through 
landmarks and I kept an eye out for fine dining. The crisp, clean air, 
seemingly limitless freedom and unlimited possibilities through 
education are the feelings that stick with me when I reminisce about 
Switzerland.</p>

<p><strong> Fall 2010 - Spring 2011</strong><br /><br/>
Fall 2010 and Spring 2011 was my reign as the elected Vice President of 
ACM. I was often the front line in representing ACM in day activities 
while the President spent time connecting ACM with administrators and 
people outside campus. I would make appearances in organization fairs 
and show off what we did as a club. I was able to link ACM to Dr. Mamo, 
spawning the Medical Applications Mobile and Online Project (MAMO).
</p>

<p>
I continued to develop TEAR with the ImagineCup team. It reached the 
semifinals in the Microsoft National and International divisions. While 
it was difficult to close the ImagineCup Project, I was proud to report 
that TEAR received honorable mention from ImagineCup judges. The team 
was able to walk away from TEAR with two years of advanced data 
structures and algorithms to be applied in future employment.
</p>

<p>
I had a taste of presidential work when the current president had to 
take a temporary leave. It was hectic coordinating meetings at first, 
but the parliamentary structure of ACM and the maturity of the people in 
it kept the club steady and productive under my temporary leadership. I 
was proud of ACM when it received Organization of the Year in the 
College of Engineering.
</p>

<p><strong>Fall 2011</strong><br/><br/>
After my year as Vice President, I became the Secretary of ACM. I kept 
detailed records of meetings and ensured the proper tracking of project 
progress. I became the representative of ACM online, maintaining the ACM 
webpage and ACM Facebook page with the assistance of the former 
secretary, Richard Wang. 
Under the management of Ben Chang, I participated in the reboot of the 
ImagineCup team to partake in the Windows Phone 7 Game Design 
competition. Ben's game idea went through many forms of revision 
for 
several months prior until we settled on our current game, Socie-D.
</p>

    ]]></activity>
    
    <desc type="text"><![CDATA[
    <p>
I am a senior at CSULB. On my spare time, I ensure the availability of CSULB ACM services, including the snack stack and the library. I enjoy videogames that invoke emotion and tug the player. I aspire to develop a game which realistically immerses the player through sophisticated emotional artificial intelligence. 
</p>
        
    ]]></desc>
    
    <memory type="text"><![CDATA[
        <p> 
The things that one will remember the most are rarely the struggles but 
more of the successes. There are obvious forms of success, like a 
project one worked hard on that was recognized, winning an election or 
receiving a grant. However, there are more subtle successes: like 
laughing over a game of the card game, Bang! Dissecting demands that 
were ridiculous and impossible but was done anyway. Making a person 
laugh or sharing a connection with a new acquaintance or an old friend. 
Going on outings or dining which strengthen the bonds of the people 
you&rasquo;re close to. 

        </p> 

        <p>
When I remember ACM, I will recall a conglomeration of success stories.
        </p>
         
    ]]></memory>
    
    <email type="text">
wiimaster1@gmail.com
	</email>
</globals>
