<?xml version ="1.0"?> 
<globals>
    <name type="text">Alex Chavez</name>
    <quote type="text">I AM ROOT</quote>
    
    <discovery type="text"><![CDATA[
        <p>
            I was in Steve Gold's 274 class back in '07 and he told us about the ACM programming team.
            I competed in the competition in that year and in '08. ACM died at that point so I didn't
            really get involved again for a while.
        </p>

        <p>However, I knew most of the members that revived it later.</p>
                
    ]]></discovery>
    
    <motivation type="text"><![CDATA[
        <p>
           In summer of 2010, I went to Switzerland for a month. Joshua Liong (ACM VP at the time), 
           Richard Wang (ACM Secretary), Matt Sguerri (Historian), and Lynn Cherngchaosil (ACM member) 
           were with me and we formed a tight group there as we traveled around (who'd have thought trains
           and buses could be so fun to ride?). I learned about the revival of ACM by the Puppetmaster Sal Llamas 
           and his cronies during Alex Ortiz's administration followed by Edgar Ortiz 
           (both of which I knew through EAT and from classes).
        </p>
        
        <p>
            I attended one meeting at ACM and noticed...I knew everyone there. Frank, Ariana, Lynn, Alex...
            I knew them all because I was TA for their 174/274 classes. Andrew, Edgar, Richard and the rest of 
            the more senior members had been in my classes at some point.
        </p>

        <p>
            I had apparently acquired a great deal of respect from everyone there and fit in naturally. 
            During the next elections, Joshua nominated me for president and it was a practically unanimous approval.
        </p>
    ]]></motivation>
    <advice type="text"><![CDATA[ 
        <p>
           Most of the advice I could give people is just repeats of what Sal says. And Sal got most of it from 3 books: 
           The Outliers, Drive, and Getting Things Done. So go and read those! Or listen to them! I got through outliers 
           and drive on  long car rides listening to the audiobooks. That was GREAT.
        </p> 

        <p>
            Advice to brand new students you need at the getgo, 
            make a tech tree of courses and plan out where you are going 
            and what classes you are taking. If you plan out your courses, you'll graduate 
            on time assuming you didn't fail Linear Algebra/Calc 2 3 times 
            (Linear Algebra is the reason I took 4.5 to graduate).
        </p>
    ]]></advice>
    <activeyears type="text">2010-2012</activeyears>
    <activity type="text"><![CDATA[ 
       <p>
       I was President of ACM for the 2011-2012 academic year (also the AESB president for the second 
       half of that year, I'd advise against anyone doing that as it was a considerable amount of work 
       to hold both those positions).
       </p>
       
       <p>
       Strangely, I don't recall ever officially being on any ACM project, 
       but I've contributed a considerable amount of resources and time to 
       the Org and its projects overall. Some of this support:
       <p>
        
        <ul>
            <li>
                Setting up ACM servers and a repository on them (a repo of pictures and an SVN repo)
            </li>
            <li>
                Acting as a contact with the CECS labs (I was a lab tech for the same years I was active in ACM)
            </li>
            <li>
                Organizing meetings and dealing with schedules (wasn't necessarily hard but was annoying...VERY annoying)
            </li>
            <li>
                Giving some of my own money to food costs as ASI refuses to let more than 20 percent of a grant go towards food (software is cheap for students, food is not)
            </li>
            <li>
                Giving advice to members of ACM.
            </li>
            <li>
                Contributing to the vast quantity of shenanigans that go on at ACM.
            </li>
            <li>
                Convinced a few influential members to join us.
            </li>
            <li>
                Managed to carry on good relations with EAT because I had long ago established a good relationship with Bob Ward. I almost became the EAT president back then but some of EAT's members from then were....douchbags, to say the least.
            </li>
        </ul> 

        <p>
            Really though, I didn't do all THAT much. I'll be the first to admit Sal Llamas was the true 
            puppet master behind the scenes. He gave us structure and a few ideas and I just went and ran with it.
        </p> 

    ]]></activity>
    
    <desc type="text"><![CDATA[
    <p>         
        As of this writing, I am a computer science grad student studying under Dennis Volper. 
        I got my BS in comp sci in Dec of 2010 (4.5 years after I entered college in 2006, yes it 
        pays to have a plan guys. That's all there is to it, besides studying obviously).
    </p>
    
    <p>
        I am an intern at IBM with several potential job offers. My area of expertise is Unix/Linux
        System Administration. Though I acquired so much Windows experience over the years, I hate 
        to admit I probably know it better. 
    </p>
    
    <p>
        Though I don't truly consider myself a coder or software engineer, I'm ironically enough better
        as those than many of my coworkers and many students (Hint: Don't declare variables named sssss and sssSSS). 
        I'm no Edgar Martinez or Andrew Meredith, but I know my way around more programming languages than I can count on one hand.
        Having seen so much code over the years, I usually help someone if they have a problem they are stuck on. 
        Helps to have more than one set of eyes guys. No reason to go through coding completely alone.
    </p>
    
        
    ]]></desc>
    
    <memory type="text"><![CDATA[
        <p> 
        Short answer? Shenanigans. Oh man was there shenanigans...
        They went on before David Nuon appeared out of nowhere but he
        was the first one to try to catalog it.
        </p> 

        <p>
        Everything from the failed yet awesome Thorbot, to the infamous I AM ROOT 
        story with a hacking a "security box" will be remembered.
        </p>
        
        <p>
        The coordination between members is also something I won't soon forget. 
        When I finally become a manager somewhere, I will remember the strategies I learned here.
        </p>
         
    ]]></memory>
    
    <email type="text">nathan2006@sbcglobal.net</email>
</globals>