<?xml version ="1.0"?> 
<globals>
    <name type="text">Frank "Viceroy" Lima</name>
    <quote type="text"><![CDATA[ <font size="2">Creativity and discipline are like yin and yang.  Both may be entirely different but without each other they attain nothing.</font> ]]></quote>
    
    <discovery type="text"><![CDATA[
        <p>I found out about the ACM just out of pure curiosity.  I was walking down the computer science building (ECS) and saw a flier posted on the wall and thought to myself, “This may be interesting, I'll check it out!”</p>
                
    ]]></discovery>
    
    <motivation type="text"><![CDATA[
        <p>I joined out of pure curiosity and to also be with my 'like-kind', meaning I wanted to be surrounded by those who were also in the same field as I was and to talk about the same subjects as well; learn and grow from one another.</p>
    ]]></motivation>

    <advice type="text"><![CDATA[ 
        <p>
           It's important to focus hard on your classes, but much more important to focus on your own projects.  The classes will teach you how to become a programmer but it is up to you to actually apply yourself and grow with the skills you learn.  By doing projects you will be able to apply yourself and truly teach yourself what it is to become a computer scientist.  Anyone can learn, but it takes a true hard worker to apply themselves.
 </p><p>
It is also important for new students to question their abilities and assess them in a positive way.  Such as, “Can I do this?” and then from that set up personal goals to change “Can I do this?” to “I CAN do this!”  Computer science may not come easy to some that is why practice is important.  Chance the “Can I's?” to the “I CAN'S!” and start small, don't plan huge projects and goals.  Start with small steps, as you learn how to 'crawl', then learn to 'walk' and from there learn to 'run'!
        </p>
    ]]></advice>
    <activeyears type="text">2009-2012</activeyears>
    <activity type="text"><![CDATA[ <p>
 

<i>2010 – 2011: Office Technician</i><br>
This was my first position with the ACM.  I was in charge of managing the ACM office as well as its computers.  I was able to rearrange the computers in such a way that it maximized space in the office.  Also, along with Ariana, we were able to completely remodel the entire office space that we had to maximize every square inch we could so that fellow ACM members could enjoy it as much as possible.</p>
<p>
<i>2011 – 2012: Vice President</i><br>
This position, I was dubbed 'Viceroy' by the 2011-2012 president Nathan Pickrell.  I worked along side Nathan to the best of my ability and also managed projects.  During this time I conducted three major projects: ACM LAN, THOR and The ACM Arcade Machine 'Rubicon'.  It was a very eventful year.  I rallied up many of the ACM members and socialized with them to see what they were doing and how they were doing.  I wanted to ensure that I was there for all the ACM members if and when they needed me.  I was also parliamentarian during certain meetings in which our president could not make.
 </p> 

    ]]></activity>
    
    <desc type="text"><![CDATA[
    <p>         
        I am a computer scientist and animator.  I started to learn how to do both at a very young age.  I began to program with QBASIC and Commodore 64 BASIC at the age of 6 years old.  My parents bought an old 286 IBM computer which could not do much of anything besides word process and program.  So I decided to make my own 'fun' with the old computer by reading up on the manual that it came with to start programming little word games and it grew from there.  At the age of 8 I began to learn how to draw and from drawing I taught myself animating using cheap flip books.  As my animation skills grew so did my programming skills.  I began to learn 3D animation at the age of 13 and C/C++ at the same age.  I then realized that I could combine both of these seemingly separate skills together to do game design! I loved games ever since I was about 3 years old when my uncle showed me Sonic the Hedgehog.
</p><p>
From the age of 13 until now I have been focusing on multimedia programming and game design within my major of Computer Science here at California State University Long Beach.  I have also taken animation and art courses here at the university and was trained by a great animation professor to improve my skills (he will never be forgotten!).  I have analyzed games for many years, seen how they function, question game design rules (and break them) to create a unique gaming experience.  Currently I am working on a light weight cross-platform graphics engine called the IONICON engine that was programed entirely in C and Assembly (for console specific reasons).  I plan on opening a software design studio known as Reticon Entertainment Technology by the end 2013.
    </p>
    
        
    ]]></desc>
    
    <memory type="text"><![CDATA[
        <p> 
        What I will remember the most through my years I have spent in the ACM are both the connections and ever-lasting friendships I have made during that time.  The ACM brings together the greatest in people; all to strive for a common cause.  It is important to work together for projects and to understand one another and by doing so, become a better person.  So to all of those who I have met at the ACM, I will remember all of you forever.
        </p>
         
    ]]></memory>
    
    <email type="text">ret.tech@gmail.com</email>
</globals>